DMYTRO OLIINYK

Junior DevOps | System administrator

ABOUT ME

IT specialist with experience in information technology, networking, technical support, system administration, and DevOps. I am a quick learner and acquire new skills. I have good communication skills, localization and problem solving, planning and time management, self-motivation and selfdevelopment. I live in **Dnipro**, **Ukraine**. Relocation is possible.

CONTACT ME

+38-050-678-23-73



devdm.dp@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/devdm/



@devdm_dp

EDUCATION

2001 - 2003

National Metallurgical Academy of Ukraine

Economic cybernetics

SKILLS

- DevOps Tools: Kubernetes, Flux CD, GitOps, Terraform, CI/CD, Helm.
- Monitoring systems: Grafana, Prometheus, Open Telemetry
- Cloud: Google Cloud Platform (GCP)
- Programming language: Python
- Soft skills: communication, teamwork, time management, critical thinking
- Other: Linux, Docker, Apache, Git, Percona MySQL, Technical support, System administration

CERTIFICATIONS

 linkedin.com/in/devdm/details/cert ifications/list

LANGUAGE

- **Ukrainian (Native)**
- **English A2 (continue to learn)**

WORK EXPERIENCE

DevOps learning path

July 2023 - recent

- DevOps techniques
- · Google Cloud Platform
- Kubernetes, Terraform, Helm
- GitOps, GitHub Actions, CI/CD
- Logging and Monitoring
- Python
- Linux administration
- Cybersecurity
- · LAMP (Apache, Percona, Python)
- · New knowledge every day

Head of Sales Department

Wissen Ukraine, July 2020 - May 2023

- · Managing a small team
- · Creating and following sales plans
- · Team building

Sales Manager, later Head of Sales Department

Atlantis systems, June 2015 - July 2020

- Sales Management
- Finding and communication with customers
- · Creating and following sales plans
- Managing a small team

System Administrator

Freelance, December 2013 - June 2015

- Computer Hardware Troubleshooting
- Technical Support
- Network Administration
- Software and Hardware Diagnostics
- Software and Hardware Installation
- Windows administration